wakoopa.com 2019-10-16

# Privacy policy - Wakoopa

## Who are we?

Wakoopa is the leading tech provider for high quality passive metering through on three screens (PC, tablet, and smartphone). We empower the consumer insights industry with the best tracking technology and the most powerful data distribution models. We also offer consumers the best user experience, as well as our respect to their personal data. 

Captured data includes all the websites, search terms, (PC) and applications (mobile) consumers interacted with. 

Wakoopa B.V., with Tax Identification Number 46.134.824-K, is registered with the Chamber of Commerce in Amsterdam (the Netherlands) under number 34266985. 

## Our commitment to protecting your data

Wakoopa is firmly committed to protecting all citizens' right to privacy. When you share your personal information with us, we believe that it is our duty to ensure that it is adequately protected. This privacy policy will tell you what information we collect about you, with what purpose, and how we protect it. 

This privacy policy applies to customers, people interested in our business and candidates who participate in any of our recruitment selection processes but not to consumers that download our software. If you are interested in knowing how our technology works in terms of privacy, please visit our [panelist data protection page](https://wakoopa.com/privacy/). 

All services provided by Wakoopa, including providing information about us or about market research topics, via newsletter or by any other means, are aimed at people over 16 years of age. 

Whenever you need to, you can exercise your rights in relation to your personal data by sending an email to [compliance@wakoopa.com](mailto:compliance@wakoopa.com) or to this postal address: 

Warmoesstraat 149   
1012 JC Amsterdam   
The Netherlands   

##  What personal data do we collect? 

The personal data that we collect, without trying to exhaust all possibilities, can be: your name, your email address, your phone number, your city of residence, the name of the company where you work, your curriculum vitae and your profile on different social networks. 

##  How do we collect this data? 

  * When you voluntarily send it to us through our website. 
  * When you provide us with your contact details in person, either at a congress, trade fair or any other similar event (or the organization provides them with your consent). 
  * When we have a professional or sales contact with you. 
  * By public access directories. 

##  For what purpose will we use your personal data? 

  * To bring you up to date on news about Wakoopa and the market research industry. 
  * To answer any query you might have sent us. 
  * To assess the candidacies in which you have applied and keep you up to date. 

You will only receive these messages if you have previously stated your wish to receive them. You will find a button on all messages to cancel your registration if you no longer wish to receive them. 

##  Will we share your information with third parties? 

No. We will never make your personal data available to companies outside of Wakoopa. 

In specific instances, companies that render IT services to us will have access to your details. 

These suppliers are not authorised to use your information for any purpose other than that for which we have contracted them. 

##  How do we protect your data? 

Wakoopa has implemented all reasonable security measures to protect your information from third parties. These measures are intended to prevent your personal data from being lost or being accessed by an unauthorized third party. 

However, like any data transmission made via Internet, there is a small risk. If you continue to use our services, we will consider that you accept this small risk which is inherent to any data transmission. 

##  Our Representative for Data Protection 

At Wakoopa we have a team specialized in Privacy and Protection of Personal Data. If you wish to contact them, you can do so by email or post to the addresses specified above. 

##  Security breaches 

In the unlikely case that any technical, organizational, or any other type of failure occurs, beyond our control, which may in some way compromise the security of your data, we will notify you immediately and inform you of the consequences that this situation may entail. In the same way, we will also inform you about the measures that we will take to solve the problem. 

Remember that, if you consider that your rights have been violated, you can always submit a claim to the competent control authority, in this case, before the Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens. 

##  Data retention policy 

Due to our intention to minimize the use of personal data, we are committed to eliminate all information about you that is not strictly necessary to provide our services. As well as erase it, in any case, after a long period of time since our last contact. 

##  Mobility of the data 

Wakoopa is an internet-based company, so our business is developed internationally, and our customers and suppliers are companies located in countries around the world. 

In this sense, Wakoopa has a worldwide network of technical or logistic providers that help us provide our services and that need to access your personal data. 

This means that we have to transfer your data to other countries to carry out our mission. However, we make sure that all these companies comply with an adequate level of security and are committed to the protection of your data. 

##  Cookies 

Wakoopa.com uses cookies to personalize your experience when visiting our website. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computer browser from a website and is stored on it. When you return to the site, the information written in the cookie can be read by the website. 

We use cookies to measure the online traffic flow on our website. We do this through analytics software called ‘Google Analytics’ which uses cookies in order to make the measuring possible. 

The stored information is exclusively used for the web consultation of Wakoopa and is only shared with Google Analytics which is only authorized to use your information to provide an analytics service to Wakoopa. 

You can also delete or update your preferences regarding cookies by visiting: 

##  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

The environment in which we work is constantly changing. Consequently, Wakoopa reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy. We recommend that you review the policy from time to time. In any case, if at any time we wish to use your data for a purpose other than that which you have authorized, we will contact you to inform you and give you the opportunity to exercise your rights in this respect.
